http://www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk/privacy-policy.htm

Skip to content
www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy covers www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk’s treatment of personal information that www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk gathers when you are on the www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk website and when you use www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk does not own or control, or to individuals that www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk does not employ or manage.
Information Collected by www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk
We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our users:
1. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.
2. Automatic Information:
o We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk cookie information, and the page you requested. www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.
o www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.
o Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.
E-mail Communications
www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. ******* may send out e-mails with *******-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. ******* cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.
The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of *******’s coolest features.
www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.
Sharing Your Information
Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.
www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk Personnel: www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk business.
Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.
Protection of www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Syndication: www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.
With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.
Children Under 18 Years of Age
You must be 13 years and older to register to use the www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk website. As a result, www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.
Conditions of Use
If you decide to visit www.eghamtownfootballclubltd1991.co.uk website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.
Egham Town Football Club Ltd
Founded 1877
as Runneymede Rovers
Honours
1913 - 1914 Hounslow & District League Champions,
1919 - 1920 Surrey Intermediate Charity Cup Winners and Challenge Cup Finalists
1920 - 1921 Surrey Intermediate League Champions, Surrey
Intermediate Charity Cup Winners
1922 - 1923 Surrey Senior League Champions and Charity Cup Winners
1926 - 1927 Surrey Intermediate Charity Cup Winners, Surrey Senior League Charity Cup Finalists
1934 - 1935 Surrey Senior League Charity Cup Finalists
1967 - 1968 Spartan League Cup Finalists, Egham Twinning Tournament Winners
1971 - 1972 Spartan League Champions, Egham Twinning Tournament Winners
1974 - 1975 Athenian League Champions, Egham Twinning Tournament Winners
1975 - 1976 Athenian League Division One Runners-Up, Egham Twinning Tournament Winners
1976 - 1977 Premier Midweek Floodlit League Champions, Egham Twinning Tournament Winners
1977 - 1978 Southern Combination Cup Winners
1980 - 1981 Egham Twinning Tournament Winners
1984 - 1985 Southern Combination Cup Finalists
1991 - 1992 Surrey Senior Cup Finalists, Loctite Trophy Finalists
1993 - 1995 (3 times in a row) Billy King Trophy Winners
1994 - 1996 (twice) Goodley Jewellers Charity Cup Winners
2002 Peter Barnes Charity Trophy (in aid of the National Deaf Children's Society)
© 2020 Egham Town Football Club
Designed by ThemeBoy
